const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'I’ve been waitlisted by UVA, what does that actually mean?',
        answer: 'You may think that you ended up on the waitlist because UVA doesn’t actually want you. The opposite is true. The easiest thing for UVA to do would be to reject you, but they have placed you on the waitlist because they earnestly hope that you will end up in Charlottesville next year.',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question:
            'Rather than go to UVA-Wise for my freshman year, why can’t I just stay at home and take community college classes?',
        answer: 'You can, but there are no guarantees. UVA-Wise has a commitment from UVA to automatically transfer courses for the Year in Wise students. No other institution has that. If you decide to take the “stay at home” route, there is no guarantee that any of the local classes will transfer and if you don’t do well in a class, it could jeopardize your admissions status at UVA. We are your guaranteed path to Charlottesville and you’ll arrive there, on time, as a sophomore.',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is the background of this program?',
        answer: 'It began in 2019 with the first class of 24. The second year we had 25. In 2021, I began actively recruiting waitlisted students and it grew to 78. In 2022, we had 70. We project 81 for 2023-2024.',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'How does the program work?',
        answer: 'You will come to UVA-Wise and complete 30 semester hours in the Fall and Spring semesters with a GPA of 3.0 or better. You can take as many hours as you want, even in the summer, but you have to complete the requirements during the Fall and Spring.',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Are there required courses?',
        answer: 'Yes, you are required to complete HIS 1850-Introduction to Appalachian Studies (3 hours), SEM 1010-Freshman Seminar (1 hour), and an upper-level Appalachia focused course (3 hours).',
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'How do I learn more?',
        answer: 'For general questions, contact Professor Brian McKnight.  If you have specific questions about the admissions process, the UVA-Wise Admissions Office can help.  For financial aid questions, reach out to the Financial Aid Office.  There is also a UVA Deferred Facebook group where you can make contact with others who are either considering the program along with you or have done so in the past.',
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question:
            'I’ve decided to take advantage of this opportunity, what do I do next?',
        answer: 'All you have to do is pay the deposit.  You can do that here.',
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'So, I’ve paid the deposit.  Now what? ',
        answer: 'Just sit tight.  It takes up to two weeks for your payment to reach every corner of our system, but once it does, you will start receiving information about the upcoming year from various offices around the College.',
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question:
            'I have questions about getting a dorm room and a roommate.  Who can I talk with? ',
        answer: 'Just call the Housing Office at 276-328-0214.',
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'I want to get a head start.  Can I take Summer classes?  ',
        answer: 'Yes, and we encourage you to.  Our Summer sessions are a great chance to get ahead of the game and they are comparatively inexpensive.  If you’re interested, let Professor McKnight know and he will advise you.',
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What should I take in the Summer?',
        answer: 'I always encourage students to take the HUM 1850 (Introduction to Appalachian Studies) course via Zoom with Professor Lloyd Tomlinson during Summer II.  Other popular courses are Microeconomics and Macroeconomics.',
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'When is orientation?',
        answer: 'There are several sessions throughout the summer, but check your UVA-Wise email for instructions to sign up.',
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'When can I sign up for classes?',
        answer: 'During orientation, you will be assigned an advisor and be able to schedule your advising appointment.',
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'What kinds of classes will I be taking?',
        answer: ' In Fall, you will likely take English Composition, Introduction to Appalachian Studies, Freshman Seminar, and a foreign language.  That’s ten hours right there.  In addition, I advise students to begin their required sequence of a Western Heritage (think Western Civilization) and a social science course (psychology, sociology, political science, economics).  In Spring, you will have more flexibility and will probably be advised to take a literature class, the second part of Western Heritage, an upper-level Appalachia course, another social science, and a class in the arts…this semester will also give you an opportunity to take an elective or two allowing you to explore the curriculum for a possible future major.',
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Will I be taking classes in my major? ',
        answer: ' No, you’re going to spend your year here with us mainly getting your core classes satisfied.  If there is room in your schedule, we will find you transferable classes in your intended discipline.',
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: 'When can I declare my major? ',
        answer: 'When you get to UVA, unless you plan to stay here for your degree.',
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: 'Should I take the Math placement exam? ',
        answer: ' Yes, as UVA only requires either one or two Math courses, we can usually get those out of the way during your year in Wise. ',
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question:
            'I took the Math placement test and it says I need to take Precalculus.  I had Calculus I, II, and III in high school.  Can I just go straight into a higher math?',
        answer: 'Every year I have a student who insists on doing this and it never goes well.  So, my position is you need to take the class you test into.  In this case, I would suggest you wait until you get to UVA to take Math since you haven’t tested into a higher Math.',
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question:
            'Can I take ENG 1030 and either SPA 1030 or FRE 1030 instead of 1010? ',
        answer: ' Yes, the English and Foreign Language faculty encourage YiW students to take these accelerated courses.',
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question:
            'I’m worried that spending my freshman year at UVA-Wise might put me behind socially at a place like UVA.  Is this true?',
        answer: ' Not at all.  One member of our 2020-2021 cohort served as the Honor Court’s Counsel for the Defense and another student was President of the Multicultural Affairs Club…at a place like UVA, they would have to wait until they were juniors or seniors to hold such positions.  At UVA-Wise, you will be surrounded by opportunities like this.',
    },
];

export default questions;
